Register of the Štefan Osuský Papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1901-1974. (Box 11-31)
  - Bouillaud, A., 1939 (Folder 14: 57)
  - Boulard, André, 1928 (Folder 14: 58)
  - Bourdelle, C., 1954 (Folder 14: 59)
  - Bourgin, Georges, 1938-1939 (Folder 14: 60)
  - Boury, Henri, 1940 (Folder 14: 61)
  - Bouvier, René, 1940 (Folder 14: 62)
  - Brada, Jiří, 1963 (Folder 14: 63)
  - Bradac, Joseph, 1939 (Folder 14: 64)
  - Braden, Ronald, 1941 (Folder 14: 65)
  - Braibant, Charles, 1938 (Folder 14: 66)
  - Branch, Rosenberg & Branch, 1950 (Folder 14: 67)
  - Brand, Walter, 1938 (Folder 14: 68)
  - Brandl, Karl, 1940-1941 (Folder 14: 69)
  - Bránická, A. X., 1939 (Folder 14: 70)
  - Branná Politika, 1938 (Folder 14: 71)
  - Bratislava (Slovakia). Univerzita. Právnická fakulta, 1938 (Box-folder 15: 1)
  - Brazil. Embaixada (Great Britain) (J. J. Moniz de Aragao), 1940-1941 (Folder 15: 2)
  - Brdlik, Vl., 1953 (Folder 15: 3)
  - Bresson, M., 1938 (Folder 15: 4)
  - Breton, Chanoine, 1939 (Folder 15: 5)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1940 (Folder 15: 6)
  - British Institute for Political Research, 1948 (Folder 15: 7)
  - Broglie, Duc de, 1939 (Folder 15: 8)
  - Brown University, 1945-1968 (Folder 15: 9)
  - Brož, Jaroslav, 1939 (Folder 15: 10)
  - Bruand, C., 1938 (Folder 15: 11)
  - Bruce, S. M., 1941 (Folder 15: 12)
  - Brucker, Wilber M., 1959 (Folder 15: 13)
  - Brumlík, J., 1939 (Folder 15: 14)
  - Brun, Dr., 1939 (Folder 15: 15)
  - Bruner, Léon, 1939 (Folder 15: 16)
  - Brunet de Coudrouniac, Gaston, 1938 (Folder 15: 17)
  - The Bryce Club, 1940 (Folder 15: 18)
  - Bullit and Middleton, 1943 (Folder 15: 19)
  - Buquet, André, 1938 (Folder 15: 20)
  - Burge, R. K., 1941 (Folder 15: 21)
  - Burger, Oscar, 1940-1941 (Folder 15: 22)
  - Bušina, Emil, 1940 (Folder 15: 23)
  - Butler, R. A., 1940 (Folder 15: 24)
  - Butter, Oscar, 1938 (Folder 15: 25)
  - Cahill, Lady, 1939 (Folder 15: 26)
  - Cain, Julien, 1940 (Folder 15: 27)
  - Campbell, Ronald, 1940 (Folder 15: 28)
  - Campinchi, Cesar, 1938 (Folder 15: 29)
  - Canada. Embassy (France) (G. P. Vanier), 1939-1950 (Folder 15: 30)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1949 (Folder 15: 31)
  - Carpentier, Louis le, 1939 (Folder 15: 32)
  - Carr, Wilbur J., 1940-1944 (Folder 15: 33)
  - Case, Joe, 1948 (Folder 15: 34)
  - Cassin, René, 1938 (Folder 15: 35)
  - Castries, Georges de, 1939 (Folder 15: 36)
  - La Cause alliée (London), 1942 (Folder 15: 37)
  - Ce soir (Paris), 1939 (Folder 15: 38)
  - Cebe, Jaroslav, 1938 (Folder 15: 39)
  - Cecil, Robert Gascoyne-Cecil of Chelwood, Viscount, 1941-1943 (Folder 15: 40)
  - Čejka, František, 1940 (Folder 15: 41)
  - The Central European Observer, 1944 (Folder 15: 42)
  - Centre Danubien, 1940 (Folder 15: 43)
  - Centre d'Etudes de Politique Etrangère, 1938 (Folder 15: 44)
  - Centre d'Expansion Française, 1939 (Folder 15: 45)
  - Centre Economique Paneuropéen, 1938 (Folder 15: 46)
  - Centre Européen de la Dotation Carnegie, 1939 (Folder 15: 47)
  - Centrokomise Ltd. (London), 1940 (Folder 15: 48)
  - Cercle de Londres du Parti Démocratique Polonais, 1944 (Folder 15: 49)
  - Cercle des Etudiants Tchéco-Slovaques à Paris, 1939 (Folder 15: 50)
  - Cercle Métropolitain de l'Empire Français, 1940 (Folder 15: 51)
  - Cercle Parisien de la Ligue Française de l'Enseignement (Léon Douarche), 1938-1939 (Folder 15: 52)
  - Cercle Universitaire, 1939 (Folder 15: 53)
  - Černý, A. L., 1939 (Folder 15: 54)
  - Černý, František, 1948-1967 (Folder 15: 55)
  - Černý, Josef, 1948-1953 (Folder 15: 56)
  - Černý, Vladimír, 1939 (Folder 15: 57)
  - Černý, Zdeněk, 1948-1949 (Folder 15: 58)
  - Cerruti, M., 1937 (Folder 15: 59)
  - Cesiano, Dinu, 1940 (Folder 15: 60)
  - České Národní Sdružení v Americe (Czech-American National Alliance), 1939 (Folder 15: 61)
  - Českomoravská-Kolben-Daněk, 1928-1929 (Folder 15: 62)
  - Československá Kolonie (Colonie Tchécoslovaque) "Krajan" (Karel Hanuš), 1938-1940 (Folder 15: 63)
  - Československá Národní rada v Americe (Czechoslovak National Council of America), 1939-1957 (Folder 15: 64)
  - Československá obec legionařská v exilu v Paříži (Czechoslovak Association of Legionnaires in Exile), 1950-1952 (Box-folder 16: 1)
  - Československá republikánská strana v exilu (Czechoslovak Republican Agrarian Party In Exile), 1956 (Folder 16: 2)
  - Československá živnostensko-obchodnická strana středostavovská v exilu (Czechoslovak Party of Middle Classes In Exile), 1949-1953 (Folder 16: 3)
  - Československé národní sdružení v Kanadě (Czechoslovak National Alliance in Canada), 1950-1957 (Folder 16: 4)
  - Československé pomocné sdružení pro Rakousko (Czechoslovak Relief Alliance in Austria), 1952 (Folder 16: 5)
  - Československé sdružení politických uprchlíků v Německu (Czechoslovak Alliance of Political Refugees in Germany), 1950 (Folder 16: 6)
  - Československý červený kříž (Czechoslovak Red Cross), 1939-1941 (Folder 16: 7)
  - Československý pomocný výbor (Czechoslovak Relief Committee in Austria), 1948 (Folder 16: 8)
  - Chadenet, Baron, 1939 (Folder 16: 9)
  - Chamberlain, Austen, 1929 (Folder 16: 10)
  - Chamberlain, Neville, 1955 (Folder 16: 11)
  - Chambre de Commerce Belgo-Tchécoslovaque (Brussels), 1939 (Folder 16: 12)
  - Chambre de Commerce de Paris, 1938 (Folder 16: 13)
  - Chambre de Commerce Franco-Tchéco-Slovaque (Paris), 1939 (Folder 16: 14)
  - Champagne Louis Roederer, 1939 (Folder 16: 15)
  - Champetier de Ribes, A., 1940 (Folder 16: 16)
  - Chappedelaine, de, 1939 (Folder 16: 17)
  - Chaptal, Emmanuel, 1940 (Folder 16: 18)
  - Charlot, Charles, 1939 (Folder 16: 19)
  - Chase National Bank (New York), 1940 (Folder 16: 20)
  - Chautemps, Camille, 1938 (Folder 16: 21)
  - Chéradarme, André, 1938 (Folder 16: 22)
  - Cherne, Leo, 1954 (Folder 16: 23)
  - Chesham Property Company Limited, 1945 (Folder 16: 24)
  - China. Embassy (Great Britain), 1940-1944 (Folder 16: 25)
  - Chocholatý, František Petr, 1939 (Folder 16: 26)
  - The Christian Century, 1960 (Folder 16: 27)
  - Christliches Hilfswerk für Heimatlose Flüchtlinge, 1948-1949 (Folder 16: 28)
  - Chrysler Corporation, 1938 (Folder 16: 29)
  - Chudoba, Bohdan, 1949-1950 (Folder 16: 30)
  - Church of England. Province of Canterbury. Archbishop, 1940-1944 (Folder 16: 31)
  - Churchill, Winston, 1943 (Folder 16: 32)
  - Chvalkovský, F., 1938 (Folder 16: 33)
  - Cicognani, Amleto Giovanni, 1953 (Folder 16: 34)
  - Cierny, Štefan, 1938 (Folder 16: 35)
  - Cihar, Jaromír, 1937 (Folder 16: 36)
  - Cipera, Dominik, 1952 (Folder 16: 37)
  - Clauzel, Comte, 1937 (Folder 16: 38)
  - Clementis, Vladimir, 1939 (Folder 16: 39)
  - Clerk, Lady, 1939 (Folder 16: 40)
  - Close Brothers Limited, 1984-1945 (Folder 16: 41)
  - Cmela, Wladyzlaw, 1942 (Folder 16: 42)
  - Cobrda, Vladimir P., 1937 (Folder 16: 43)
  - Cohen, Benjamin, 1941-1947 (Folder 16: 44)
  - Cohn and Marks, 1954 (Folder 16: 45)
  - Cole, Ashley T., 1937 (Folder 16: 46)
  - Colgate University, 1945-1959 (Folder 16: 47)
  - The College, Winchester, 1944 (Folder 16: 48)
  - Collège de la Malgrange, 1940 (Folder 16: 49)
  - Collège d'Europe, 1956 (Folder 16: 50)
  - Collège Libre des Sciences Sociales (Jean Hennesey), 1939 (Folder 16: 51)
  - Collon, J., 1938 (Folder 16: 52)
  - Columbia. Consulado (Lyon) (Paul Auloge Duvivier), 1938 (Folder 16: 53)
  - Columbia Broadcasting System Inc. (London), 1944 (Folder 16: 54)
  - Comité Central des Réfugiés, 1939 (Folder 16: 55)
  - Comité d'Aide aux Volontaires Anciens Combattants, 1939 (Folder 16: 56)
  - Comité d'Aide Sociale aux Réfugies Tchécoslovaques, 1952-1953 (Folder 16: 57)
  - Comité de Co-Ordination Franco-Anglais, 1939 (Folder 16: 58)
  - Comité d'Organisation de la Cérémonie d'Inauguration de la Statue du Maréchal Foch au Carrefour de l'Armistice - Compiègne, 1937 (Folder 16: 59)
  - Comité d'Organisation du Congrès d'Etudes Internationales, 1937 (Folder 16: 60)
  - Comité Français de Coopération Européenne, n.d. (Box-folder 17: 1)
  - Comité Français d'Union Economique et Douanière Européenne, 1938 (Folder 17: 2)
  - Comité Français pour l'Europe Libre, 1953 (Folder 17: 3)
  - Comité International pour la Diffusion Artistique et Littéraire par le Cinématographe, 1938 (Folder 17: 4)
  - Comité National Français, n.d. (Folder 17: 5)
  - Comité National pour la Jeunesse, 1937 (Folder 17: 6)
  - Comité Nobel du Parlement Norvégien, 1950 (Folder 17: 7)
  - Comité Protestant des Amitiés Françaises à l'Etranger, 1940 (Folder 17: 8)
  - Commemorative Committee of the Slovak National Uprising, 1964 (Folder 17: 9)
  - The Commercial Cable Co., 1943 (Folder 17: 10)
  - Commission Française de Coopération Intellectuelle, 1938 (Folder 17: 11)
  - Commission Permanente d'Organisation des Congrès de Chimie Industrielle, 1937 (Folder 17: 12)
  - Committee for a Free Estonia, 1953 (Folder 17: 13)
  - Common Cause, Inc., 1949-1950 (Folder 17: 14)
  - La Confédération Internationale des Travailleurs Intellectuels, 1937 (Folder 17: 15)
  - Conférence Internationale des Associations de Mutilés de Guerre et Anciens Combattants, 1937 (Folder 17: 16)
  - Connely, Willard, 1947-1948 (Folder 17: 17)
  - Contemporary Review, 1941 (Folder 17: 18)
  - Continental Press Agency, 1939 (Folder 17: 19)
  - Contre révolution, 1938 (Folder 17: 20)
  - Coronet Magazine, 1950 (Folder 17: 21)
  - Cortney, Philip, 1949 (Folder 17: 22)
  - Coste, Brutus, 1957-1968 (Folder 17: 23)
  - Cotins, Arthur, 1947 (Folder 17: 24)
  - Cotnareanu, Léon, 1938-1941 (Folder 17: 25)
  - Cotton, D., 1945 (Folder 17: 26)
  - Coudenhove-Kalergi, R. N., 1938 (Folder 17: 27)
  - Coulondre, Robert, 1940 (Folder 17: 28)
  - Cox, A. P., 1941 (Folder 17: 29)
  - Cranborne, Viscount, 1940-1941 (Folder 17: 30)
  - Crémieux, Benjamin, 1938 (Folder 17: 31)
  - Cretzianu, Alexandre, 1950 (Folder 17: 32)
  - Croix-Rouge Française, 1938-1939 (Folder 17: 33)
  - Crusade for Freedom, Inc., 1957-1959 (Folder 17: 34)
  - Csaky, Geza, 1937 (Folder 17: 35)
  - Czarate Maidenhead, 1940 (Folder 17: 36)
  - Czech, Ludvik, 1938 (Folder 17: 37)
  - Czechoslovak Free Trade Union Federation, 1957 (Folder 17: 38)
  - Czechoslovak Independent Brigade, 1938? (Folder 17: 39)
  - Czechoslovakia. Haut Commissariat au Tourisme (Paris), 1938-1939 (Folder 17: 40)
  - Czechoslovakia. Konzulat (Algiers) (Vaclav Láska), 1938 (Folder 17: 41)
  - Czechoslovakia. Konzulat (Bombay), 1940 (Folder 17: 42)
  - Czechoslovakia. Konzulat (Marseille), 1939 (Folder 17: 43)
  - Czechoslovakia. Ministerstvo zahraničního obchodu, 1948 (Folder 17: 44)
  - Czechoslovakia. Velvyslanectví (United States), 1947 (Folder 17: 45)
  - Cziechanowski, Jan, 1940 (Folder 17: 46)
  - Dackett, W., 1941 (Folder 17: 47)
  - Daily Telegraph and Morning Post, 1948 (Folder 17: 48)
  - Daladier, Edouard, 1939-1968 (Folder 17: 49)
  - Damidot, 1945 (Folder 17: 50)
  - Dastich, František, 1953 (Folder 17: 51)
  - Dautry, R., 1937 (Folder 17: 52)
  - David, André, 1939 (Folder 17: 53)
  - Debré, Robert, 1939 (Folder 17: 54)
  - Decori, Félix, Madame, 1938 (Folder 17: 55)
  - De Courcy, Kenneth Hugh, 1941-1948 (Folder 17: 56)
  - Decugis, Madame, 1939 (Folder 17: 57)
  - Delavergne, James, 1939 (Folder 17: 58)
  - Delbos, Yvon, 1938 (Folder 17: 59)
  - Demaret, Georges, 1939 (Folder 17: 60)
  - Dendur, Jan, 1939 (Folder 17: 61)
  - Denis, Ernest, 1939 (Folder 17: 62)
  - Denní Hlasatel, 1948 (Folder 17: 63)
  - Deschamps, Louis, 1939 (Folder 17: 64)
  - Deslandres, Maurice, 1939 (Folder 17: 65)
  - Desmars, J., 1938 (Folder 17: 66)
  - Desvoyes, Madame, 1939 (Folder 17: 67)
  - Deutsch, Louis, 1939 (Folder 17: 68)
  - Digeon, Madame, 1939 (Folder 17: 69)
  - Les Dispensaires Parisiens de Nuit, 1938 (Folder 17: 70)
  - Dobias, Premysl, 1948-1949 (Folder 17: 71)
  - Doche, Jean, 1938 (Folder 17: 72)
  - Donn, Raymonde, n.d. (Folder 17: 73)
  - Dorian, Henry, 1939 (Folder 17: 74)
  - Dotation Carnegie pour la Paix Internationale (Malcolm W. Davis), 1939 (Box-folder 18: 1)
  - Drbal, Zdeněk, 1939 (Folder 18: 2)
  - Drdák, František, 1939 (Folder 18: 3)
  - Dreyfus, Louis, 1939 (Folder 18: 4)
  - Dubček, Alexander, 1968 (Folder 18: 5)
  - Dubois, Pierre, 1939 (Folder 18: 6)
  - Dubský, A., 1948 (Folder 18: 7)
  - Ducháček, Ivo, 1939. (Folder 18: 8)
    Includes his description of the situation in the Protectorate of Bohemia and Moravia
  - Duff, Edward, 1950-1952 (Folder 18: 9)
  - Duhamel, Georges, 1939 (Folder 18: 10)
  - Dulignier, Henri, 1939 (Folder 18: 11)
  - Dulles, John Foster, 1947 (Folder 18: 12)
  - Dunn, Halbert L., 1954. (Folder 18: 13)
    Includes his paper entitled "Creative Destiny"
  - Dupierreux, R., 1938 (Folder 18: 14)
  - Dupré-Debouit, Marie-Anne, 1920 (Folder 18: 15)
  - Durand, Maurice, 1936-1939 (Folder 18: 16)
  - Duras, Victor Hugo, 1939 (Folder 18: 17)
  - Durrande, Pierre-Alexis, 1939 (Folder 18: 18)
  - Durtain, Luc, 1938-1939 (Folder 18: 19)
  - Dutauzin, Madeleine, 1945 (Folder 18: 20)
  - Dutreux, Auguste, 1939 (Folder 18: 21)
  - Duval-Guth, Armand, 1944 (Folder 18: 22)
  - Duvernoy, Georges, 1939 (Folder 18: 23)
  - Dvorník, František, 1939 (Folder 18: 24)
  - Dyer, Louise B. M., 1939 (Folder 18: 25)
  - East European Labor Institute, 1952-1953 (Folder 18: 26)
  - Ebor, William, 1940 (Folder 18: 27)
  - Ecer, Bohuslav, 1939 (Folder 18: 28)
  - L'Ecole Française de Bruxelles, 1937 (Folder 18: 29)
  - Ecole Municipale de Physique et de Chimie Industrielles, 1938 (Folder 18: 30)
  - Edard, Notaire, 1938 (Folder 18: 31)
  - Eden, Anthony, 1939-1944 (Folder 18: 32)
  - Eglise Evangélique Luthérienne de France, 1938 (Folder 18: 33)
  - Eisenberg, Robert, 1939 (Folder 18: 34)
  - Ekor, William, 1941 (Folder 18: 35)
  - Elbel, Paul, 1938 (Folder 18: 36)
  - Elie-Bois, Rita, 1958 (Folder 18: 37)
  - Elslegerová-Puklová, 1938 (Folder 18: 38)
  - Emanuel, R., 1945 (Folder 18: 39)
  - Emissions Radio-Normandie, 1938 (Folder 18: 40)
  - Enfière, André, 1938 (Folder 18: 41)
  - Engelmann, L., 1939 (Folder 18: 42)
  - L'époque, 1939 (Folder 18: 43)
  - Epstein, Julius, 1948 (Folder 18: 44)
  - Eros, Imro, 1953 (Folder 18: 45)
  - Euphonia, Association Internationale, 1937 (Folder 18: 46)
  - L'Europe nouvelle, n.d. (Folder 18: 47)
  - European Movement, Central and Eastern European Commission, 1951-1953 (Folder 18: 48)
  - Evêché de Blois, 1940 (Folder 18: 49)
  - The Evening Bulletin and the Sunday Bulletin, 1948 (Folder 18: 50)
  - Ewerts, Karl J., 1953 (Folder 18: 51)
  - L'exportateur français, 1938 (Folder 18: 52)
  - L'Exposition Internationale, Comité d'Accueil, 1937 (Folder 18: 53)
  - L'Exposition Internationale de la Chasse, 1938 (Folder 18: 54)
  - Exposition Internationale de Paris 1937, 1938 (Folder 18: 55)
  - L'Express, 1953 (Folder 18: 56)
  - F.O.P. des Associations de Mutilés, Veuves, Orphelins de la Guerre et Anciens Combattants, 1939 (Folder 18: 57)
  - Fajfr, General, 1937 (Folder 18: 58)
  - Fakhry, 1938 (Folder 18: 59)
  - Fasquelle Editeurs, 1939 (Folder 18: 60)
  - Faucher, General, 1939 (Folder 18: 61)
  - Fédération des Emigrés d'Allemagne en France, 1939 (Folder 18: 62)
  - Fédération des Professeurs Français Résidant à l'Etranger, 1938-1939 (Folder 18: 63)
  - Fédération Française des Etudiants Catholiques, 1937 (Folder 18: 64)
  - Fédération Interalliée des Anciens Combattants, 1938 (Folder 18: 65)
  - Fédération Internationale de la Presse Technique et Périodique, 1937 (Folder 18: 66)
  - Fédération Internationale Libre des Déportés et Internés de la Résistance, 1952 (Folder 18: 67)
  - Fédération Nationale des Volontaires de Guerre, 1939 (Folder 18: 68)
  - Fédération P.E.N., 1938 (Folder 18: 69)
  - Fedinec, Ladislav, 1950-1953 (Folder 18: 70)
  - Fels, A. de, 1939 (Folder 18: 71)
  - Le Figaro, 1939-1950 (Folder 18: 72)
  - Filipowicz, Tytus, 1943-1949 (Folder 18: 73)
  - Filo, Kornel, 1955 (Folder 18: 74)
  - Fischer, J. L., 1939 (Folder 18: 75)
  - Fischer, Victor and Alice, 1941 (Folder 18: 76)
  - Flanderka, Otakar, 1939 (Folder 18: 77)
  - La Flèche, 1937 (Folder 18: 78)
  - Fleischman, Franta, 1941-1943 (Folder 18: 79)
  - Foerster, J. W., 1939 (Folder 18: 80)
  - Fontenay, Mr et Mme de, 1938 (Box-folder 19: 1)
  - Foreign Affairs, 1948-1949 (Folder 19: 2)
  - Forgeot, Pierre, 1939 (Folder 19: 3)
  - Forman, Josef, 1938-1948 (Folder 19: 4)
  - Fort, F. L., 1941 (Folder 19: 5)
  - Fortune, 1953 (Folder 19: 6)
  - Fould, René, Madame, 1939 (Folder 19: 7)
  - Fragner, Jan, 1939 (Folder 19: 8)
  - France. Ambassade (Germany), 1950 (Folder 19: 9)
  - France. Ambassade (United States), 1947-1950. (Folder 19: 10)
    Includes correspondence with Henri Bonnet
  - France. Assemblée Nationale, 1952 (Folder 19: 11)
  - France. Assemblée Nationale. Chambre des Députés, 1938 (Folder 19: 12)
  - France. Assemblée Nationale. Sénat, 1939 (Folder 19: 13)
  - France. Conseil Economique et Social, 1966-1973 (Folder 19: 14)
  - France. Conseil Municipal de Paris, 1940 (Folder 19: 15)
  - France. Légation (Czechoslovakia) (Léopold Victor de Lacroix), 1937-1939 (Folder 19: 16)
  - France. Légation (Iran), 1938 (Folder 19: 17)
  - France. Ministère de l'Air, n.d. (Folder 19: 18)
  - France. Ministère de l'Intérieur, 1939 (Folder 19: 19)
  - France. Ministère de la Marine, 1938 (Folder 19: 20)
  - France. Ministère de la Santé Publique, 1938 (Folder 19: 21)
  - France. Ministère des Affaires Etrangères (F. Seydoux Fornier de Clausonne), 1938-1970 (Folder 19: 22)
  - France. Ministère des Colonies (Paul Devinat, Max Brusset), 1937-1939 (Folder 19: 23)
  - France. Ministère des Finances, 1949 (Folder 19: 24)
  - France. Ministère du Blocus (Georges Pernot), 1940 (Folder 19: 25)
  - France. Ministère du Commerce et de l'Industrie (Gentin), 1938-1939 (Folder 19: 26)
  - France. Préfecture de Police, 1940 (Folder 19: 27)
  - France. Préfet de la Charente, 1938 (Folder 19: 28)
  - France. Préfet de Loire-et-Cher, 1940 (Folder 19: 29)
  - Franck, Marcel, 1939 (Folder 19: 30)
  - Francl, François, 1968 (Folder 19: 31)
  - François-Poncet, André, 1961 (Folder 19: 32)
  - Franěk, Mikuláš, 1948-1959 (Folder 19: 33)
  - Frankelová, Magda, 1940 (Folder 19: 34)
  - Franklin, William M., 1939 (Folder 19: 35)
  - Fraštacký, Rudolf, 1949 (Folder 19: 36)
  - Free Europe, 1941-1943 (Folder 19: 37)
  - Free Europe Organizations and Publications, 1962 (Folder 19: 38)
  - Freeman, Arnold, 1941 (Folder 19: 39)
  - Fried, Arnost, 1940-1952 (Folder 19: 40)
  - Friedenau, Theo, 1953-1957 (Folder 19: 41)
  - Friedlander, Robert A., 1964 (Folder 19: 42)
  - Friends of the Polish-Czechoslovak Union, n.d. (Folder 19: 43)
  - Frossard, L. O., 1940 (Folder 19: 44)
  - Fuller, Henry R., 1947-1949 (Folder 19: 45)
  - Fullerton, Morton, 1939 (Folder 19: 46)
  - Fusek, Eduard, 1950-1954 (Folder 19: 47)
  - Futak, Jan, 1940 (Folder 19: 48)
  - Gabra, B. G., 1942 (Folder 19: 49)
  - Galko, Jan, 1939 (Folder 19: 50)
  - Gaster, Sacha de, 1949 (Folder 19: 51)
  - Gaubert, Ernest, 1938 (Folder 19: 52)
  - Gaulle, Charles de, 1959 (Folder 19: 53)
  - Gaultier, Paul, 1937-1939 (Folder 19: 54)
  - Gauthier, Paul, 1937 (Folder 19: 55)
  - Gavrilovich, M., 1944 (Folder 19: 56)
  - Georges, General, 1938 (Folder 19: 57)
  - Georges-Picot, Colonel, 1940 (Folder 19: 58)
  - Geringer Press, Inc., 1948 (Folder 19: 59)
  - German Information Center, 1963 (Folder 19: 60)
  - Germany. Botschaft (France) (Madame la Comtesse de Welczeck), 1938 (Folder 19: 61)
  - Gharib, Mr. and Mrs., 1938 (Folder 19: 62)
  - Giansanti Coluzzi, Countess, 1938 (Folder 19: 63)
  - Gibian, Věra, 1950-1955 (Folder 19: 64)
  - Gineste-Tesi, Anna, 1937 (Folder 19: 65)
  - Giraud, Emile, 1954 (Folder 19: 66)
  - The Girl Guides Association, 1945 (Folder 19: 67)
  - Goldmann, Nahum, 1939 (Folder 19: 68)
  - Gorel, Michel, 1938 (Folder 19: 69)
  - Gorell, Elizabeth, n.d. (Folder 19: 70)
  - Gosset, A., 1939 (Folder 19: 71)
  - Gounin, E., 1939 (Folder 19: 72)
  - Les Grandes Conférences des Ambassadeurs (Raymond Poincaré), 1923-1939 (Folder 19: 73)
  - Grandmaison, Robert de, 1939 (Box-folder 20: 1)
  - Grange, Baron de la, 1939 (Folder 20: 2)
  - Grange, Henri, 1939 (Folder 20: 3)
  - Graux, Lucien, 1938-1939 (Folder 20: 4)
  - Great Britain. Embassy (France). (Folder 20: 5)
    Includes correspondence with Eric Phipps, 1939-1940
  - Great Britain. Embassy (United States), 1944-1953 (Folder 20: 6)
  - Great Britain. Foreign Office, 1943 (Folder 20: 7)
  - Great Britain. High Commissioner for New Zealand, 1943 (Folder 20: 8)
  - Great Britain. Ministry of Economic Warfare, 1941 (Folder 20: 9)
  - Great Britain. Ministry of Information, 1941 (Folder 20: 10)
  - Great Britain. Ministry of Town and Country Planning, 1943 (Folder 20: 11)
  - Greater Hartford Council for Unesco, 1941-1950. (Folder 20: 12)
    Includes correspondence with Alfred Zimmern
  - Greece. Legation (Great Britain) (Politis), 1938-1940 (Folder 20: 13)
  - Green, Ernest, 1941 (Folder 20: 14)
  - Grenier, F., 1939 (Folder 20: 15)
  - Grey, E., 1912 (Folder 20: 16)
  - Griffin, Joan, n.d. (Folder 20: 17)
  - Gromada, Thaddeus V., 1963 (Folder 20: 18)
  - Grunebaum-Ballin, P., 1939 (Folder 20: 19)
  - Grunov, Heinrich, 1938 (Folder 20: 20)
  - Gudin du Pavillon, 1939 (Folder 20: 21)
  - Guerdan, L. G., 1939 (Folder 20: 22)
  - Guérin, Albert, 1938 (Folder 20: 23)
  - Guibal, 1939 (Folder 20: 24)
  - Guillaume, Maurice, Madame, 1939 (Folder 20: 25)
  - Guilliermond, Professeur, 1938 (Folder 20: 26)
  - Guillon, Gustave, 1938 (Folder 20: 27)
  - Habe, Hans, 1939 (Folder 20: 28)
  - Hadji Minache, G., 1939 (Folder 20: 29)
  - Haight, John McV., 1958-1961 (Folder 20: 30)
  - Hájek, František, 1939 (Folder 20: 31)
  - Halamski, 1939 (Folder 20: 32)
  - Hanák, Miloš, 1938-1964 (Folder 20: 33)
  - Hardman, D. R., 1941 (Folder 20: 34)
  - Harmaniec, Milan, 1947-1948 (Folder 20: 35)
  - Harper's Magazine, 1950 (Folder 20: 36)
  - Harvard-Thane, G., 1943 (Folder 20: 37)
  - Harvey, J., n.d. (Folder 20: 38)
  - Hašek, Joseph, 1967 (Folder 20: 39)
  - Hauner, Edgar Stanislav, 1939 (Folder 20: 40)
  - Havas, Emil, 1951 (Folder 20: 41)
  - Havlasa, Jan, 1939 (Folder 20: 42)
  - Hazen Hyde, James, 1939 (Folder 20: 43)
  - Heckert, Robert, 1950 (Folder 20: 44)
  - Hedges and Butler, Ltd., 1943 (Folder 20: 45)
  - Heidrich, Arnošt, 1950-1967 (Folder 20: 46)
  - Hejduk, B., 1960 (Folder 20: 47)
  - Helfert, Vladimir, 1938 (Folder 20: 48)
  - Henderson, Arthur, 1930 (Folder 20: 49)
  - The Herald Tribune, 1941 (Folder 20: 50)
  - Herbert, Lucien, 1939 (Folder 20: 51)
  - Herbillon, Pierre, 1939 (Folder 20: 52)
  - Hermite, Ambassadeur, 1939 (Folder 20: 53)
  - Herriot, Edouard, 1938-1950 (Folder 20: 54)
  - Herron, George D., 1918-1925 (Folder 20: 55)
  - Heveder, L. l', 1940 (Folder 20: 56)
  - Hickson, G. H., 1941 (Folder 20: 57)
  - The Highway, 1942 (Folder 20: 58)
  - Hilibert, S. E., 1942 (Folder 20: 59)
  - Hill, Jozef, 1915 (Folder 20: 60)
  - Hillenkoetter, R. H., 1947 (Folder 20: 61)
  - Hines, Walker D., 1921 (Folder 20: 62)
  - Hirschfeld, Eugène, Madame, 1937 (Folder 20: 63)
  - Hirth, Eric, 1941 (Folder 20: 64)
  - Hlaváček, Ladislav, 1938 (Folder 20: 65)
  - Hlavatý, Václav, 1960 (Folder 20: 66)
  - Hodges, Charles, 1950 (Folder 20: 67)
  - Hodža, Fedor, 1948-1962., See also Hillenkoetter, R. H. (Folder 20: 68)
  - Hodža, Milan, 1937-1943 (Folder 20: 69)
  - Hoetzl, J., 1938 (Folder 20: 70)
  - Holdos, Ladislav, 1965 (Folder 20: 71)
  - Holub, V., 1956-1957 (Folder 20: 72)
  - Holý, Václav, 1948-1949 (Folder 21: 1)
  - Holy Trinity Slovak Evangelical Lutheran Church, 1952 (Folder 21: 2)
  - Hood College, 1949 (Folder 21: 3)
  - Hora, Václav, 1937 (Folder 21: 4)
  - Horáček, Jan, 1969 (Folder 21: 5)
  - Horák, Josef, 1937 (Folder 21: 6)
  - Horn, Ernest, 1942 (Folder 21: 7)
  - Horna, Richard, 1937-1938 (Folder 21: 8)
  - Horníček, Jaroslav, 1939 (Folder 21: 9)
  - Horvath, 1940 (Folder 21: 10)
  - Hospodárské Rozhlady, 1937 (Folder 21: 11)
  - Hostovský, Egon, 1950 (Folder 21: 12)
  - Houdard, E. M., Madame, 1939 (Folder 21: 13)